<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="context">
    <item>"I'm MFamilys,I fuck the dog today,:)\n
        　Just for test this lewd and small arrow\n
          Son of bitch,need three lows"</item>
    <item>"\t\t        Five Benefits of Run\nWhether you already have a regular running routine or you've been meaning to start one, consider these 5 benefits of running in the morning. While running is widely considered to be one of the best ways lose weight and stay healthy, very few people talk about when to do it. Here are five ways in which running in the morning can benefit you:
无论你是否已经养成了跑步的习惯，或是一直想开始跑步，考虑一下在早上跑步的5大好处。尽管跑步是公认的最佳减肥及保健方式，真正着手去做的人并不多。以下是晨跑的5大优点：
1.Weight-loss: One of the primary reasons regular runners pound the pavement is to burn calories and to lose weight. Some experts, however, believe that running on an empty stomach in the morning burns more calories than any other time of the day. This has to do with two things: if your body's metabolism gets turned on early, it keeps going longer, thus burning off more fat. Secondly, if you run on an empty stomach, your body is forced to use the energy that is most available to it at the time, which on an empty stomach is your body's store of fat. Make running your first activity of the day if you want to amp up those weight-loss benefits.
1.减肥：有跑步习惯的人，最主要的原因通常都是为了燃烧卡路里和减肥。一些专家认为早上空腹跑步比别的时段能燃烧更多的热量。主要有两个原因：当身体的代谢被提前激发时，它能坚持更久，因此燃烧更多热量；此外，空腹跑步能迫使你的身体利用当下所能得到的能量，而空腹的时候，这所谓的能量就是你体内的脂肪。把跑步变成每天第一项运动吧，你能更快地减肥。
2.Peace of mind: Most runners will agree that running helps clear the mind and get those creative juices flowing. Problems are solved and ideas are born as the road glides along under your feet. This probably has to do with the release of hormones called endorphins, which have a peaceful, calming, and refreshing effect on your mind and body. So why not kick in those powerful endorphins early in the day? If you know you're going to have a rough day ahead of you, a good way to preemptively combat those stresses is to run in the morning. Try it out; you might just find that your work day seems a lot less stressful than it usually is.
2.平和心境：很多跑步的人都同意一个说法，那就是跑步能帮你平和心境，并激发灵感。当你的双脚不停地迈过大地时，解决问题的办法和新主意都会出现。这可能与一种叫内啡肽的激素释放有关。它能平复心境，并消除疲劳，无论生理还是心理上。所以何不在清晨来一剂内啡肽？若你感到今天将是压力山大的一天，早起晨跑以抵抗它是个好主意。试试看吧，你会发现这一天似乎也没有预想得这么糟！
3.No excuses: By running in the morning, all of the typical excuses for not exercising (e.g. a lack of time, being too tired after work, or missing happy hour with your buddies) can be put to rest. Now those after-work hours can be used to take care of errands or loaf on your sofa, completely guilt-free. Getting your exercise done first thing in the morning also gives you that jump start you need to keep moving throughout the day, which helps rid you of excuses for other important tasks that you would normally not feel like doing.
3.拒绝借口：晨跑能消灭所有那些让你不锻炼的借口，比如“没时间”、“下班后太累啦”、“要跟朋友聚会呢”等等。下班后你可以为所欲为，无论是做事还是蜷进沙发，而不需要心存负罪感。晨起锻炼同样也能给你一个充满活力的开头，帮助你戒掉那些为了不大想做的事而千方百计想出来的借口。
4.Less pollution: Among the many benefits of running in the morning is getting out on the road before the cars and busses beat you to it. The exhaust left behind from vehicles can increase the risk of heart disease and cancer, so slip on your jogging shoes in the early morning if you want to breathe in the cleanest air possible.
4.空气更清新：晨跑还有一个好处，那就是可以避免吸入车辆尾气。尾气会增高心脏病和患癌几率。所以还是早起，穿上跑鞋，去一天中最清新的空气里奔跑吧。
5.Go farther: There is no doubt about it; the air is not only cleaner, but also much cooler before the sun's rays have begun to bake the road under your feet. Running in the morning is the best way to avoid hot weather, heat stroke, and stifling humidity. Runners that exercise in a cool climate can often run longer and go farther than those who work out in the heat.
5.让你跑得更远：毫无疑问，早晨不仅空气清新，同样也异常凉爽。在毒辣辣的太阳照射大地前跑吧。晨跑是避免热天、中暑、和沉闷潮湿感的最好选择。在凉爽天气中跑步的人们通常可以比热天中的人们跑得更远更久。
Now set your alarm clocks tonight because these benefits of running in the morning are worth waking up early for.
今晚就设好闹钟吧！这些好处完全值得你早起去奔跑。"</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>
    <item>MFamilys</item>

</string-array>
</resources>